sunricher.com 2018-08-02

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Thank you for visiting sunricher.com. We understand your privacy is important to you.

To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site.

## The Information We Collect

We collect transaction information and email addresses. We collect only the minimum information necessary to complete your order online; this is the same information required to complete telephone orders - name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, and payment information. We require customer email address for online orders so that we may notify you of your order status or merchandise return status  
If you purchase from sunricher.com, your email will be added to the sunricher.com's e-newsletter list and database. We may send you emails promoting our products, announcing special events and offering other special limited-time discounts, such as free shipping, that may be used by online customers. You may opt-out of receiving any email promotional communication at any time.  
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 7 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

## Information Collected by Sunricher APP

When you use the APP of Sunricher Technology Limited, all personal information generated is limited to your use in the APP, we will not upload your personal information, all your personal information will not be leaked and used for other purposes.

Currently ,we are using Piwik analytics to collect limited data for website performance and user accessibility improvement ONLY.

## How We Use the Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.   
We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements or to contact you about your account with us.  
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs or services.  
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.  
Employees of Sunricher.com who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Sunricher.com.  
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.  
Finally, we will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

## Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

Sunricher.com may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

## Cookies

To enhance your experience with our site, many of our Web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files placed in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.  
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our site. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

## Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the Sunricher.com. online policy or its implementation, you may Contact Us.
